https://www.monster.co.uk/inside/privacy/home.aspx

Welcome to the Monster Privacy Centre
Monster is committed to protecting the privacy of our users and strives to provide a safe user experience. Our Privacy Centre is available to help you better understand how Monster collects and uses your information and the choices you have for protecting it.
The Privacy Centre is home to our Privacy Policy and contains information About Our Ads. Our Privacy Policy is designed to inform you of our privacy practices using language that is as clear and concise as possible. We provide information About Our Ads to explain our approach to advertising and how we make it more relevant to you.
We've also provided information about cookies on Monster along with a list of Frequently Asked Questions about privacy at Monster. If you have a privacy-related question that isn't addressed in the FAQs or elsewhere in the Privacy Centre, please contact us.
For information on staying safe online and conducting a safe and secure job search, visit our Security Centre.
For information on customers’ call recordings, visit the Call Recordings Notice.
We occasionally track seeker mouse movements and clicks to improve user experience using Hotjar. If you'd like to opt out of tracking click here.
To see a list of partners that help us deliver relevant advertising, please click here.
Main Topics
Privacy Policy
Monster collects personal information from you and uses it to help you connect with employers and other job seekers with similar interests. Our Privacy Policy describes your privacy choices and how we handle your information.
Privacy FAQs
Do you have questions about privacy on Monster? Do you wonder what happens to the personal information you give to us? Read our Privacy FAQs for more information.
About Our Ads
Monster uses your information to show you ads that are more relevant to your interests. For more information, read the About Our Ads section of the Privacy Centre.
Cookie Info
For more information about cookies on Monster and your privacy choices regarding cookies, read the Cookie Info section.
